class QuizQuestions {
  String question, a, b, c, d;
  int ans;

  QuizQuestions({
    required this.question,
    required this.a,
    required this.b,
    required this.c,
    required this.d,
    required this.ans,
  });
}

List<QuizQuestions> contents = [
  QuizQuestions(
      question: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit ipsum amet?',
      a: 'Lorem ipsum',
      b: 'ipsum dolo',
      c: 'sit ipsum',
      d: 'dolor sit',
      ans: 1),
  QuizQuestions(
      question: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit ipsum amet?',
      a: 'Lorem ipsum',
      b: 'ipsum dolo',
      c: 'sit ipsum',
      d: 'dolor sit',
      ans: 4),
  QuizQuestions(
      question: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit ipsum amet?',
      a: 'Lorem ipsum',
      b: 'ipsum dolo',
      c: 'sit ipsum',
      d: 'dolor sit',
      ans: 3),
  QuizQuestions(
      question: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit ipsum amet?',
      a: 'Lorem ipsum',
      b: 'ipsum dolo',
      c: 'sit ipsum',
      d: 'dolor sit',
      ans: 4),
  QuizQuestions(
      question: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit ipsum amet?',
      a: 'Lorem ipsum',
      b: 'ipsum dolo',
      c: 'sit ipsum',
      d: 'dolor sit',
      ans: 1),
  QuizQuestions(
      question: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit ipsum amet?',
      a: 'Lorem ipsum',
      b: 'ipsum dolo',
      c: 'sit ipsum',
      d: 'dolor sit',
      ans: 2),
  QuizQuestions(
      question: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit ipsum amet?',
      a: 'Lorem ipsum',
      b: 'ipsum dolo',
      c: 'sit ipsum',
      d: 'dolor sit',
      ans: 3),
  QuizQuestions(
      question: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit ipsum amet?',
      a: 'Lorem ipsum',
      b: 'ipsum dolo',
      c: 'sit ipsum',
      d: 'dolor sit',
      ans: 4),
  QuizQuestions(
      question: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit ipsum amet?',
      a: 'Lorem ipsum',
      b: 'ipsum dolo',
      c: 'sit ipsum',
      d: 'dolor sit',
      ans: 1),
  QuizQuestions(
      question: 'Lorem ipsum dolor sit ipsum amet?',
      a: 'Lorem ipsum',
      b: 'ipsum dolo',
      c: 'sit ipsum',
      d: 'dolor sit',
      ans: 2),
];
